Ifeoluwase Adeleke

IUNIOR WER DEVELOPER

Profile

Junior full-stack web developer with 2years work experience able to build responsive web applications from the ground up. Proficient with HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript. Hands on experience with CSS frameworks like Bootstrap and Materialize. Experience in building beautiful responsive apps with JavaScript frameworks like EJS, React.js, Next.js and React Native and quality REST APIs with Nodejs and Express.js. I also write Technical Articles on different programming topics on Medium.

Employment History

Junior Web Developer, Ancla Technologies, Yaba, Lagos

APRIL 2022 — NOVEMBER 2022

- Led weekly meetings with clients and in-house staff to go over websites progress reports.
- Built new features and improved existing ones for Obade web app that improved user payment experience.
- Collaborated to create strategic initiatives to design, code, and test solutions.
- Effectively coded software changes and alterations based on specific design specifications.
- Tested, deployed, and maintained web applications.
- Worked with React Native to convert figma designs to mobile apps to create new software updates for VetroPay.

Website Developer (contract), Konnect.ws, Remote

SEPTEMBER 2021 — MARCH 2022

- Worked to build competing website in regards to content, look, and feel with React.js
- Planned software architecture and built Rest API on the back-end with Nodejs using Sequelize as ORM and MySQL as Database.
- Integration of third-party payment systems such as Flutterwave and Paystack.
- Integration of third-party APIs for file storage and website feature implementation.
- Tested, deployed, and maintained web application.
- Effectively multi-tasked and worked well with internal and external teams.

Website Developer, Kescreative, Ikotun, Lagos State

APRIL 2021 — JANUARY 2022

- Collaborated with a team of creatives to develop a now defunct edu-tech website using React.js.
- Developed a Rest API with Nodejs and Mongoose to service over 175 school pupils watching tutorials.
- Tested, deployed, and maintained web application on Namecheap and cPanel.

Education

Details

5, Sanusi Street, Council bus stop, Ikotun, Lagos, Nigeria +234-8132277316 eadelekeife@gmail.com

Technical Skills

HTML5 & CSS3

JavaScript

React.js

Node.js

React Native

MongoDB / MySQL

jQuery

Git / GitHub / BitBucket

Sequelize / Mongoose

Bootstrap / SASS

Ant Design / Materialize

SOL

Languages

English

Yoruba

Links

My Portfolio

 $\underline{\mathsf{GitHub}}$

<u>LinkedIn</u>

Medium

Twitter

Hobbies

Football, Travelling, Listening to Music, Watching Stage Drama Performances.

BSc Chemistry, Federal University of Agriculture, Abeokuta,

OCTOBER 2017 — FEBRUARY 2023

SSCE, Sigma Bond Academy, Ikotun, Lagos State

JANUARY 2011 — MAY 2014

Courses

Code with Node JS - 2021, Udemy

FEBRUARY 2021 — MAY 2021

Modern React with Redux, Udemy

OCTOBER 2020 — DECEMBER 2020

The Modern JavaScript Bootcamp Course (2020), Udemy

MAY 2020 — JULY 2020

Build Responsive Real-World Websites with HTML and CSS, Udemy

APRIL 2020 — APRIL 2020

Web Design for Web Developers: Build Beautiful Websites, Udemy

APRIL 2020

Internships

Frontend Developer at Titan Galaxy, Abeokuta

OCTOBER 2020 — APRIL 2021

- Helped to build and add new features to FunaabPay website
- Helped to achieve a consistent look and visual theme across the website by promoting uniform fonts, formatting, images, and layout.
- Successfully identified, diagnosed, and fixed website problems, including broken links, typographical errors, and formatting issues.
- · Helped to build and upload new client websites

References

References available upon request